learnstagelighting.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Learn Stage Lighting .com

**Privacy Policy for www.learnstagelighting.com**

**_If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at questions@learnstagelighting.com._**

At www.learnstagelighting.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.learnstagelighting.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.learnstagelighting.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.learnstagelighting.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

This includes cookies from Facebook.com which are used for advertising as well as analytics.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.learnstagelighting.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.learnstagelighting.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

Facebook Advertising

Twitter Ads

Pinterest Ads

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.learnstagelighting.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.learnstagelighting.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.learnstagelighting.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Personal Information:**

Any personal information that you submit on Learnstagelighting.com will be stored in one of 2 secure places:

Gumroad will collect information securely for payment and delivery of products.

Aweber will collect information such as name and email for marketing purposes.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not solicit or knowingly gather information from any children under the age of 13.   In the event that we find out about such information, either from the child or a parent, we will delete said information as fast as possible.  If you believe you may have any information about a child under 13 who’s information we have stored, please email us at questions@learnstagelighting.com immediately!

**Changes to this Policy**

LearnStageLighting.com may at any time change or modify this privacy policy.  So check back periodically if you have concerns.

LearnStageLighting is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to (“learnstagelighting.com” ([amazon.com](http://amazon.com/), or [endless.com](http://endless.com/), MYHABIT.com, SmallParts.com, or AmazonWireless.com).
